lecremedelacrumb.com 2018-06-29

# About Tiffany | Food Blogger | Creme de la Crumb

Hi there, I’m Tiffany – cook, photographer, and lover of salted caramel. I started Creme de la Crumb in 2013 as a way to catalog my kitchen endeavors. I instantly fell in love with the whole process of cooking, photographing, eating, writing, and sharing recipes with others. I really believe that great meals don’t have to be difficult, time-consuming, or expensive. That’s why I focus on sharing taste-tested recipes that are quick, easy, and crazy delicious.

My husband is my official taste-tester, and editor in chief. Together with our twin toddlers, we spend our free time boating, traveling, and eating lots and lots of tacos.

I love to stay connected with my readers! You can find me on [Pinterest](https://www.pinterest.com/cremedelacrumb/), [Instagram](https://instagram.com/cremedelacrumb1), [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/cremedelacrumbblog), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/CremedelaCrumb1), [Google +](https://plus.google.com/113284184665675365902), or send me a good old-fashioned email at tiffanyazure (@) yahoo (dot) com.

**Recipe Development and Food Photography:  **I would love to work with your brand to create recipes using your products and photograph dishes for use on packaging, website, or other uses as agreed upon. I’m also available to be a recipe contributor for other websites offering taste-tested recipes to their readers. Please contact me for rates and other questions.

**Brand Ambassadorships** : I love to create long-lasting relationships with brands and am open to working on campaigns long-term with products and brands that I love.  Together we can promote a positive image for your brand and business.

**Reviews & Giveaways: **I am available to write about product reviews and share giveaways with companies and brands that I believe in or think would be a good fit and high value for my readers.

**Brand Sponsored Travel** : I would be thrilled to represent your brand and travel to various events/conferences, headquarters, touring facilities, etc. and share my experiences with my readers through blog posts and social media outlets.

**Freelance Food Writing & Photography: **I would love to write and/or photograph editorial content for your website or various publications.

Please email me at tiffanyazure(at)yahoo(dot)com for more details or to request a media kit.

Have a question, want to work with me, or just want to say hi? Send me an email or use the form below!

> “A photographer went to a socialite party in New York. As he entered the front door, the host said ‘I love your pictures – they’re wonderful; you must have a fantastic camera.’ He said nothing until dinner was finished, then: ‘That was a wonderful dinner; you must have a terrific stove.” -Sam Haskins

**My Approach** : Simple – I try to make food look as good as it tastes in real life. My goal is to capture food in all of its natural beauty because the food is beautiful, it tastes lovely, and it aids in creating beautiful memories. A picture is worth a thousand words, but I try to make mine say just one: yum!

**My Camera** : From the day I started taking photographs of food and started this blog (May  2013) til present, I have used the same camera for all of my pictures – a Canon 7D,  unfortunately, it has been discontinued. The CANON EOS 6D is a similar camera. I love the 7D, someday I may upgrade but this camera has treated me well, and I have grown immensely with it. It has incredible capabilities and allows for so much versatility in photography. If you are just getting started with photography and are in the market for something a little less expensive, I recommend the Canon EOS Rebel T2i  or the Canon Rebel, both of which will give you a great starting place and room to grow.

**My Lens** : From May 2013 to present, all of my food photographs have been taken with a Canon EF 50mm f/1.8 II Camera Lens lens. It is incredibly affordable and produces excellent, very sharp photos. I have my eye on a Canon EF 100mm f/2.8 Macro Lens but haven’t invested yet.

**My Editing Software** : From May 2013 till present, I use Photoshop CS6 and love it. It is quite expensive to purchase, but you can sign up for a monthly Digital Membership which makes it much more affordable. Another good option is Adobe Photoshop Lightroom 5. Many of my blogger friends use and love this program.

**My Lighting** : 100% el natural. I do not use any artificial lighting in any of my food photography.

**Tripod** : I also use a tripod for nearly all of my food photography.

If you’re looking to get started or to improve your food photography skills, this book is AMAZING. Lindsay from Pinch of Yum has shared her secrets in this easy to follow guide to food photography. I used this book when I was starting out, and it made every bit of difference in taking my pictures from “okay” to “WOW.” Worth every penny!

Looking for more tips, tricks, and photography resources? [Check out this post](https://www.lecremedelacrumb.com/food-photography-tips-tricks/).

## Privacy

**Your Privacy  **is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Simple Plate has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

#### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, Simple Plate will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

Under our Terms of Service, children under 18 are not allowed to access our service.

#### Collection of Personal Information

When visiting Simple Plate, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice visit the NAI at http://www.networkadvertising.org. To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices.

When we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site, these companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising. org/managing/opt_out.asp

#### Links to Third Party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Creme de la Crumb then you may contact us by clicking Here.

* * *

## Disclosure

This policy is valid from 31 October 2013. This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact me.

This blog accepts various forms of cash posting, sponsorship, or paid topic insertions. We do accept paid advertising in various forms. Sponsored or paid insertions are clearly marked as such.

The compensation received for advertising will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as coming from that network.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blog owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.
